<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
  <item>
    <post_id>73</post_id>
    <post_date>2019-06-21 05:26:48</post_date>
    <post_title>10 Tips to design a effective business card:</post_title>
    <post_content>&lt;!-- wp:image {"id":95} --&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;img src="https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/vcard.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-95"/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though the world
is marching towards going paperless more and more, business cards
still holds an important place when it comes to business. Business
cards are considered as the key marketing tool even today. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A business card
measuring 2 inches by 3.5 inches must be designed to convey overall
image of the business at a single glance.  However a business card
cannot tell the whole story of a company, but must create a
professional image to the people outside. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Fundamentals of a business card: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The first and foremost fundamental of a business card is to have all
the information right 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:list --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Name
	&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Designation
	&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Company
	name 
	
	&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Email
	&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Phone
	number
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:list --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Knowing to striking a right balance between text and visuals is
necessary. It is important to think where the eye lands first in a
business card and designing it accordingly is another tip to be kept
in mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 2. Special Finishes: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; An instant way to attract using a business card is by using special finishes which includes foil blocking, spot –UV, metallic inks etc..It is important to make the business card more tactile, impressive visually and must be unforgettable. There are many printing companies who offer different options. Take some time to talk to them before finalizing.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 3. Shape of the card: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Another great way to create an impression using the business card is
by giving it a beautiful cut. One can use die to change the shape of
the card by rounding the corners or by just cutting shapes from the
centre. Die-cutting allows cutting out any shape and in bulk.  There
are many professionals who help in designing a better business card.
It is always a better idea to talk to them and gain some knowledge
before finalizing a design. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 4. Materials used: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Although most business cards are printed on cards one can choose to
get more creative. There are many options available including
plastic, wood or even slate. Different materials comes with different
pricing it is important to analyse and decide the one that does not
burn your pocket&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 5. Choose a font: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The font used in a business card is as important as the design,
material and the finish. A right font used will not irritate the
client and will make them go through the business card completely.
Making them glued to card a little longer will make them remember the
business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 6. Make it useful: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
There is lots of paper around everybody in the form of news papers,
magazine, books, note books, flyers, pamphlets etc. There are few
people who hold of every bit of paper that they receive but few are
ruthless and throw away in the first opportunity. To avoid such risks
one can be a little more creative while designing a calling card. For
instance one can design a business card as a holder for simple things
like clips, needles etc.. or as a miniature phone holder. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 7. Do not use it like a brochure: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Though it is necessary to have all important information in a
business card, but should never be used as a brochure. If one likes
to put in a little more information on the business card, the
backside of the card can be used. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8.  Look after the cards: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Business cards must be maintained well to keep its sheen. Maintaining
them using a card holder will help business cards stay in shape. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 9. Recycle: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As the business grows the business cards also takes different shape.
Old business cards can be given new life by recycling them. There are
lots of professionals in the market who can help recreating the old
business cards into new ones. Spend some time and let the creativity
flow. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;      &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 10. Say no to errors: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As business cards are a great means of marketing for a business it is
important to keep it free of errors.  There can be nothing worse than
having a typo in the email address or name. It is important to double
check before sending it for printing. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;</post_content>
    <post_author>1</post_author>
    <post_url>https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/?p=73</post_url>
    <post_image>https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/vcard.jpg</post_image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <post_id>70</post_id>
    <post_date>2019-06-21 05:26:03</post_date>
    <post_title>A guide to trouble shoots your air conditioner:</post_title>
    <post_content>&lt;!-- wp:image {"id":91} --&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;img src="https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/acrepair-1024x512.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-91"/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever
asked yourself “Hey is the AC working?” after the first season?
It is better to address it before the mercury soars. Like any other
appliance air conditioner also needs little maintenance now and then
for it to perform well. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So here is a
simple guide to identify common problems and to troubleshoot them.
This simple guide will help you save few hundred bucks on AC repair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:list {"ordered":true} --&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Dirty
	filter:
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:list --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Regardless of the type of air conditioner used a clogged filter will
arrest air flow. This eventually leads to low efficiency and reduces
the ability to effectively cool the air. It is mandatory to check the
air filters periodically and clean them. Since centralized AC’s run
continuously the filters get clogged up much faster. It is mandatory
to check them and clean them every month.Filters must be checked
periodically even when there are pets at home. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 2.  Sunny inside? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
By installing a AC unit in a room that receives most sunlight then
the unit has to work much harder to cool the air in the room.  A
better solution to it is to move it to a shadier space or by keeping
the shades or curtains drawn helps prevent the rooms getting heated
up. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 3.   Leakage of warm air: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The seals around the AC have to be checked now and then to ensure hot
air is not getting in or cool air is not seeping out. It is necessary
to reseal the unit with weather strip. It is always better to use
manufacturer’s installation and safety hardware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 4.  Vibrating window AC: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The whirl of the fan, sound of the compressor cycling on and off, and
Air conditioners makes lots of noise. These are considered as normal.
But when you hear a vibrating sound then this means the unit is not
installed properly. It is necessary to reinstall the unit according
to the manufacturer’s instructions. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 5.  Checking thermostat setting: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Air conditions, these days come with smart or programmable
thermostats. This helps you to easily control the temperature to a
comfortable setting when you are in and a bit higher temperature when
you are not in the room.  It is important to make sure the thermostat
is not exposed to direct sunlight which may cause the machine to
register wrong temperature. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 6.   Check the registers: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
By regularly cleaning the registers of dust you can experience good
performance of the AC. It is also necessary to check the registers in
the air conditioners are not blocked by furniture or other objects
that stops easy air flow. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 7.  Plants and compressors: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The outdoor compressor must be free of any disturbances caused by
plants or building structure for proper air flow. One has to make
sure that there are at least 2 or 3 feet space between the compressor
and any other object. There has to be at least 5 feet clearance
between the top of the unit and any other object. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 8.  Annual check up: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Finally, an annual check up by a heating, ventilation and air
conditioning expert (HVAC) will help determine serious problems on
time. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;                                                                     &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;</post_content>
    <post_author>1</post_author>
    <post_url>https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/?p=70</post_url>
    <post_image>https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/acrepair-1024x512.jpg</post_image>
  </item>
  <item>
    <post_id>67</post_id>
    <post_date>2019-06-21 05:24:43</post_date>
    <post_title>Exercise and Vegan Diet:</post_title>
    <post_content>&lt;!-- wp:image {"id":93} --&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;img src="https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/diet.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-93"/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:image --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you one among
those people who believe vegan diet can be a hurdle when it comes to
fitness goals? The answer is a big “NO”. By following a proper
regime and having a professional fitness expert next to you,
achieving your fitness goals becomes easier.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breaking those
myths:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are lots of
myths that revolve around veganism and fitness. One of the greatest
myths is that one cannot achieve fitness goals by following vegan
diet. Whereas many people who follow plant-based diet stay in great
shape and achieve fitness goals far more easily. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making food your
best friend:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making food your
friend is a healthy habit. Emotions are closely tied to what we eat.
Following a plant based food leads to quick weigh loss as it is
absorbed more quickly into the system. When you try to shift to plant
based life style it is important to consume more meals in order to
maintain certain level of energy and weight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alkaline foods do
the magic:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally a plant
based diet is considered to be alkaline in nature. Unlike acidic
foods like meat or dairy products which increases acidity of the
blood. Alkaline foods help body to flourish and enable faster post
work out recovery. So when you are in the process of recovery it is
necessary to consume more alkaline foods. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is all vegan food
healthy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The answer to the
question might shock many. There is a category of vegan food called
junk food. Taking vegan pizza or a burger every day will definitely
not help you achieve your fitness goals or a six pack will not
appear. To achieve your goal to shred some weight you have to adhere
to a strict, healthy vegan diet. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The power of
protein:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a
misconception among people that by following a vegan diet, one cannot
get complete protein. There are many foods that are considered as
good sources of protein, some of them are hemp, nut-based milk, nuts
and seeds, quinoa, tofu, lentils, seitan and beans that can help you
to going. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not get
addicted to food:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! food can be
a most addictive thing that we pump into our bodies. If you try to
cut down animal based diet that has been consumed for many years
would definitely give you withdrawal symptoms. But this is not
something to worry about, these are the ways of body detoxifying
itself. Just hold on for a while and you will be amazed to note the
body getting adjusted to the change. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay positive:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being positive
and clinging to it for a while is a herculean task. Doubts would
arise as people around you might discourage you for your decision of
going vegan. When you are in a spree of changing lifestyle many
people around you might not support you. This might leave you a
little low but keeping the spirits up and going will enable you to
achieve your fitness goals.  Hire a fitness expert as they can help
you identify what your body needs and plan workout based on it. Get
ready to experience an incredible transition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;

&lt;!-- wp:paragraph --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;                                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- /wp:paragraph --&gt;</post_content>
    <post_author>1</post_author>
    <post_url>https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/?p=67</post_url>
    <post_image>https://a2itproducts.com/emirates_quotations/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/diet.jpg</post_image>
  </item>
</items>
